McLaren's entering Extreme E because first we think it's a fascinating championship.
We have a long history in pioneering and innovation,
which is clearly what the Extreme E championship has been founded on
and sustainability and diversity, two very important issues in the world today
and we feel we can use the racing platform to put on a great show,
but also to accelerate our learning in sustainability
and being able to contribute to making the world a better place.
McLaren is basically motorsport.
McLaren is the history of motorsport.
McLaren is the glory.
McLaren is the titles in many different championships.
And then also McLaren is the view of the future.
And McLaren represents really what we want to have in Extreme E:
a great competitor, a team that is a winner
but also a team that shares our values for the preservation of our planet, of the environment.
I think it's a great addition to Extreme E.